Then I took it out to eat it .
It was ...
this big .
Yellow , tasty looking sponge cake .
I held it in my bosom all day .
Then I saw a girl carrying her sister on her back .
Looked obvious they were starving .
So pale , weak and helpless
I turned away to eat it .
But I ended up giving it to them .
It must 've been warm since
I carried it around all day .
I didn 't know if I 'll ever have cake like that again .
She gobbled it down and shoved some in her sisters mouth .
Think God will remember that ?
Though its been 30 years ?
Absoposilutely .
Remembering is His specialty .
Of course .
That song , Father Can you play it for me , again ?
You can do CPR , right ?
Go !
Stop !
Again !
200 Joules .
Charge .
Those who seek direct communication with God are prone to self-hatred ...
The Devil will eat right into you .
As St. Bruno said , ' Suicide is to die a martyr for Satan . '
It 's worse than first degree murder .
It 's worth a life sentence ... in hell .
20 Hail Mary 's , get lots of sun
and take a cold shower .
Get Gods help through science and take some anti-depressants
Stop thinking about killing yourself .
And ... forget the bastard who dumped you .
Father ...
Ill deal with the bastards and the worldly matters .
You just stick to praying , Father .
Ask the bishop to send me to Emmanuel Labs , please ?
The Vatican does not approve of that experiment .
Sarah died on Monday even after 8 surgeries .
Hyo-sung went into a coma yesterday .
It kills me to watch them dying .
No one knows what really goes on at that lab .
I want to save people .
I told you to go to med school since you were in the crib ,
study ophthalmology , and heal my eyes .
But Father , I must go and ...
Enough ! I 'll just give you absolution .
Stick to the confession ! Geeze !
Dear patients , I regret not seeing you before I left .
I was busy preparing for my sudden vacation .
I packed a bunch of things .
But they say to bring my body only .
The monastery prepared a luxurious hotel for me .
Fr . Emmanuel Memorial Biochemical Labs At times like this I 'm glad I joined The Order .
Grant me the following in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ
Like a leper rotting in flesh , let all avoid me .
Like a cripple without limbs , let me not move freely .
Remove my cheeks , that tears may not roll down them .
Crush my lips and tongue , that I may not sin with them .
Pull out my nails that I may grasp nothing .
Let my shoulders and back be bent that I may carry nothing .
Like a man with tumor in the head let me lack judgment .
Ravage my body sworn to chastity leave me with no pride ,
and have me live in shame .
Let no one pray for me .
But only the grace of the Lord Jesus Christ have mercy on me .
A month has gone by already .
Watching the grand view through the window is more fun than TV .
The hotel owner gave me her best room ,
saying I 'm handsome .
Thanks to all the sunlight my skin is tanned and peeling .
Time of death , 3 : 31 p.m.
Grant me the following
in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ .
Like a leper rotting in flesh , let all avoid me .
Like a cripple without limbs ...
His skin ...
let me not move freely ...
6 months later
Touch my leg , Father !
Please pray for me , Father !
Please , Father ?
My daughter has leukemia !
You know how much he talked
Saying the pain is killing him ,
but still on and on about the sponge cakes , this and that .
That very day ,
I was about to doze off after a long night shift when I was paged .
A thought crossed my mind .
What if I walked a little slowly , just a little .
If he passed away now , he 'd only be two months earlier than expected .
I thought my life would be a lot more bearable without him .
By the time I arrived on dragging feet
hypoxia had lead to a brain damage and he had already gone quiet .
He 's been in that state for a year now .
He 's still my patient , and ...
every time I see him , I feel ...
You feel terrible about it ?
Not ... terrible ,
but uncomfortable .
Thought I 'd let him go two months earlier and he 's still around after a year .
It 's a miracle that he is still alive .
They say it 's thanks to your prayers .
Dermatologists would be happy to see this .
All the numbers indicate you 're healing up incredibly fast .
What 's it like , being a man of miracle ?
I 've become strangely sensitive to sound and smell .
It makes me feel dizzy and nauseous .
The symptoms aren 't related to EV ,
but more like a pregnancy .
I heard ...
people are coming to seek prayers from The Bandaged Saint ?
Don 't know how that nonsense started .
Though I did hear of some people getting cured .
Guess it can have a psychological effect .
After all , you 're the only one who survived out of 50 volunteers .
Right ?
Wow ! You 're so lucky !
Are you the miracle survivor out of 5007
My son has cancer !
Please pray for him !
It 's just a psychological effect Theres nothing I can do .
Look .
Channel 9 won 't come on , Mom .
Let 's pray kids .
Did you ever live in Busan ?
We are gathered here to pray for Kang-woo .
Born under Your grace and love ,
embracing even a wounded street dog ...
he was a kind hearted boy .
Remember his goodness and have mercy on him .
In Jesus ' name we pray .
- Amen . - Amen .
I don 't believe in this but since it 's from an old friend ...
Now , I recognize you , son .
Sorry . You 're a Father , now .
I 'm sorry , Father .
You used to come over for noodles .
Fifth grade , right ? You lived at the church orphanage ?
My son could never pass stray
cats and was so good to the orphans .
Your sister was so shy and ran out whenever I came over .
She had calluses on her feet and Kang-woo made me touch them .
Her parents rented a small room in our house .
Her father was a high school drop out .
This is my blood shed for you so that sins may be forgiven .
One day , they left her in my room and said they 'd be back soon .
But they never came back !
So I took the three-year-old
in and raised her like a daughter and puppy .
Happy Hanbok Shed call me ' mommy '
I 'm her mommy-in-law , now .
Marriage was no big deal .
She just moved from sleeping in my bed to Kang-woo 's .
Why 'd you buy the laver at that place again , Mom ?
I told you it 's no good and the owner 's a cocksucker
You hate Kimbap ?
No , I 'm sensitive to smell these days .
I suddenly got a whiff of blood .
Kang-woos home .
- Mom , I caught a cold ! - What ?
Hi , Sang-hyun !
I told you to wear your long johns .
- Were here , too - Welcome .
My friend the priest .
This is our dam 's manager and his wife .
It 's an honor , Father I 'm Young-du
She 's a Filipina so she 's Catholic .
Say hello , Evelyn .
- Tae-ju ! - How 've you been ?
Here comes the Police Chief !
Please , I quit the force a long time ago .
He 's the dam 's security head This is Fr . Hyun , Sang-hyun
Hello .
Do you like fishing Father ?
Get on his good side and you can fish there though its banned .
Daytimes a bit tricky . Come by at nights .
- Have a seat , Father - Let 's get started .
Koreans don 't appreciate Mahjong .
Would you like to play , Father ?
- Sorry . I don 't know how - I see .
Did I tell you about Father Hyun praying for Kang-woo ?
I was standing right next to my son .
Suddenly , I felt something hot come down on my head .
I felt tingly all over like someone was poking me with needles .
Then my boy said ' It feels hot right here , Mom . '
Then the cancer vanished .
It vanished ?
You always feel tingly cuz of your blood pressure .
But I did a biopsy just in case .
The endoscope showed it was esophagus cancer .
Women shouldn 't get sedated endoscopes .
Doctors secretly rape them .
I win !
Three closed triplets !
That 's 8 points .
Can we turn the heater down ?
But I 'm cold .
Kang-woo says he 's cold !
Thank you very much .
I 'm losing so much .
Instead of the hot water bag !
I 'm going down to get the lights in the store .
Don 't you love our Mahjong gang ?
Wednesdays . Mercury . Water .
Oasis ! How 's that for our gang 's name ?
She 's a Catholic Veronica .
She was in a bad hit-and-run .
Lost a lot of blood .
She doesn 't have much time .
Let this water call to mind your baptismal sharing ...
in Christ 's redeeming passion and resurrection .
Veronica . Make your confession .
By the power the apostolic See has given me in the name of the ...
Father , the Son , and the Holy Spirit , I grant you
a plenary indulgence and ...
pardon for all your sins .
Amen .
Through this holy anointing ...
may the Lord in his love and mercy help you ...
with the grace of the Holy Spirit .
And ...
may the Lord who frees you from sin ...
save you and raise you up .
Amen .
Where 'd you wander off to this time ?
I woke up I was at the pharmacy .
And some man walked past .
Aren 't there pills for sleepwalking ?
I should lock your room from the outside .
Should 've got me pills for my cold .
Weren 't you cold ?
You never catch a cold .
She 's a Yeti , Mom .
Smells like when you had gastritis .
I 'll go find the pills .
Must you do this to believe me ?
Don 't grab my heart so hard .
When I drank Hyo-sung 's blood ...
the blisters disappeared .
It 's as if the vampire cells suppressed EV .
But , it doesn 't last very long .
Father ...
I didn 't choose the blood that was transfused into me !
You know I went there to do good !
Now , I thirst after all sinful pleasures .
But how can I get human blood without killing !
First ...
The Lord said not to worry about what to eat .
For He feeds even whe birds in the sky .
Here .
I think I won .
Small four winds !
Closed , half flush , bonus 3 points !
30 bucks ! You lose !
Some priest . From Macao or something ?
He 's the only one who survived out of 500 .
500 , yeah right .
When did you go out ?
I didn 't see you .
It 's ah ... kind of an infectious disease .
Scary , isn 't it ?
How different ... without his glasses .
How can you get infected ?
Not through a kiss for sure .
I never kissed anyone in my life .
Until now .
I don 't get shy .
I didn 't run out cuz I 'm shy .
Back in Busan ...
It 's cuz I was sick of everything .
The mom , idiot son , and the dark , damp house .
The non-stop weepy , old songs .
I waited for you to come .
The orphanage boy ...
I waited for you ...
when I was young ...
cuz the idiot liked you .
When you came , he left me alone .
I 'm not a shy person .
I run out on my bare feet ...
to escape from this hell sooner .
I even run out from my sleep .
They think its sleepwalking .
I feel awake only then and asleep the rest of the time .
Honey !
Tae-ju !
Hot water bag !
Tae-ju ?
Tae-ju !
You bitch !
There she goes again .
I fed you and raised you !
Go put her to bed !
You can 't even change your husband 's hot water bag ?
How dare you !
I win .
Let go !
Stomach troubles ? What took you so long ?
Eat up other 's money and you 'll get diarrhea .
What 's got into you ?
This looks fun .
So exciting to touch .
I could do it all night , too .
You don 't even know how to do it .
Me ?
I know how to do it .
I 'm good .
They are on fire !
I can 't wait till next Wednesday .
Then how about Sundays , too ?
Why not ?
Well ...
It 's Easter Sunday I 'm staying at the hospital .
It 's best to leave things in wanting .
Did you touch her ?
I kissed her and held her .
Undress her ?
Not completely .
The Good Book says to cut off the hand that sins ...
but no matter how many times I do ... I can 't control my heart .
Mom ...
I ...
can 't live like this anymore .
I want to help the needy .
Maybe I can volunteer at a hospital or something .
On Sundays .
Sin of heart is okay .
That is a common sin so it can be easily forgiven .
But you must not taint your body with sin .
Once you fall , there 's no stopping it .
Keep cutting and cutting .
Cut away anything and everything , to keep your body from sins .
Holding her is like being in the water .
Almost doesn 't feel like a body .
Anyway , I cannot believe it 's a sin .
Thank you for coming .
Don 't come again .
But I came to help the needy .
Its a bigger sin for a priest .
I 'm not Catholic .
To me , you 're just a needy , single man .
We can both go to hell for this .
I don 't have faith I 'm not going to hell .
But I ...
I have a terrible disease .
I 'm too damn healthy .
Just once , I wish I could be sick in bed .
It 's okay .
Hyo-sung 's in a coma .
Unless his vitals drop no one will come in here at nights .
Sorry , I hurt you .
No , its good .
Its strange , but good .
Is it supposed to feel this good ?
What 's wrong with me ?
Are other women like this ?
Am I a pervert ?
Did you eat ?
Ah , yes .
Can we meet during the day next week ?
Daytimes a bit ...
We could be together longer .
I don 't want to keep my disease a secret from you .
| I am ...
a kind of a ...
I don 't kill anyone you know .
Hyo-sung ...
He loved helping the hungry .
He 'd offer me his blood , if he wasn 't in a coma .
If you only heard the sponge cake story .
No one blames someone for getting hurt in an accident !
No one gets criticized for having cancer !
I went there to do good !
So what if I 'm a vampire ?
Did you like me cuz I 'm a priest ?
Its not that , is it ? That 's just my job .
Being a vampire is like having different palates ...
or different biorhythms don 't you think ?
When two people are in love , does it really matter ?
No , what I mean is ...
You hate that I 'm a vampire ?
Think I could 've slept with you if I wasn 't ?
How could I have sex with you ?
As just a priest ?
Come with me .
I 'll take you away from this hell .
You liked doing it with me Kang-woo 's no fun .
Tae-ju ?
What 's going on ?
The toilet 's not flushing .
It 's going down now .
Closing time .
Hello ?
How can ...
someone become a vampire ?
Can you catch it through sex ?
Can you turn me into one ?
Vampires are ... cuter than I thought .
Can you bend this ?
What for ?
Can you jump down from here ?
Too high ?
I 'm ready .
Did Kang-woo do that ?
Does he hurt you often ?
Not often ...
Want me to rip him up like that coin ?
I lived as their dog my whole life ...
feeding the idiot , washing him and even helping him masturbate .
You know ...
I 'm practically a virgin .
He 's ...
Such an idiot , he won 't take his medicines unless I take them first .
I don 't know how [ can still be alive after all the weird medicines I took .
That idiot doesn 't like me doing volunteer work .
I 'll kill them both , Kang-woo and his mother !
We don 't have much time . Hold me , now .
Does it hurt ?
Can 't you volunteer somewhere else ?
Mental hospitals are so scary .
Drink it .
Can 't you go back to the lab ?
Ask if there 's any way for a cure ?
Sunlight is bound to hit me on my way there .
Sunlight ...
I wish I can see the sunrise over the sea before I die .
What are you thinking !
Vampires can 't see the sunlight !
I don 't care if it 's at night .
The moon , the stars and even a firefly ...
Be the miracle worker !
Make the blind see !
Give me the vampire blood !
It even killed EV !
Please , Sang-hyun !
Come here !
Sang-hyun ! Father Hyun !
Please !
Just a little bit , please ?
I 'm no longer a priest nor a friar .
Forget the rules ! Forget the Vatican !
I 'm leaving !
Father Hyun ! Father Hyun !
I don 't know why you wandered astray .
But I know you 'll get through this .
I took pity on you when you were young .
We had you over for noodles .
You can stay here as long as you want .
Thank you .
Tae-ju ...
She 's really good at heart .
I 'm giving the shop and everything to her .
Did I do it too hard ?
It 's perfect .
One more time , then ?
Why do I always get mixed up with the freaks ?
One does it once every 5 years and the other , 5 times a day ...
Did you think about what I said ?
Let 's say I run away with you , Father .
Told you I 'm not a priest anymore !
You can sleep during the day . There are many people who live like that .
Poets , writers , they all work at night .
Or , pretend you 've been in New York till now , and haven 't got used to the time difference .
I 'll take care of everything at night .
I feel like I can do anything . I could drive a night cab .
And suck the blood off customers when you get hungry ?
Why would I run away with a cab driver ?
When this house will eventually be mine .
Good night .
Sweet dreams .
Get out ! Go !
Hurry !
Go ! Someone will see you !
No ! Don 't !
♪ The seagulls flying in the distance ...
♪ I called , but no response .
♪ O , my hometown by the waters where bright blue stars glisten ...
♪ in my dreams full of sorrow .
Remember Tae-ju when she was young ?
Wasn 't she cute ?
When she was 12
she woke me up and showed me her panties .
Said she peed blood .
Cuz mom worked her day and night with needlework .
We cried together all night .
Planning on taking all night ?
It 's only 9 o 'clock .
The hospital and police questioning will take hours .
What if the sun comes up ?
I said , no !
Just a little bit ?
They 'll find out with an autopsy !
Why go somewhere else for blood ?
We have blood right here .
Put the knife down .
Yeah , put it down .
No ! Don 't come near me !
It 's not too late ... If I pull him out now , he 'll live .
Tell me now ! You really want him dead ?
If we do this , it 'll make us happy ?
For sure .
Really ?
Of course , silly .
One female . Unconscious . Well be going soon .
Don 't mention that I let you fish here .
I 'll take care of everything .
Such a terrible thing , this ...
Hey , what are you doing ?
Accidents happen in the blink of an eye , eh ?
You need the body to close the case .
You can go home now .
Can it be so hard to find ?
We 'll call you if we find him .
Even if we can 't , he 'll eventually float up
It 's a lake . He can 't go anywhere . You need to see a dermatologist .
Wait !
You 'll be fined for fishing in a restricted area .
Yes .
Father Hyun ... Father ...
He became ill again for our sins !
Grant me the following
in the name of our Lord Jesus Christ .
Like a leper rotting in flesh , let all avoid me .
Like a cripple without limbs
let me not move freely .
Remove my cheeks
that tears may not roll down them .
There was a house at the bottom of the lake .
A submerged village .
I thought he was dead .
But when I went up he 'd float up , too .
So I put him in a closet in the house
and a big rock on his chest .
What if he comes out and chases me ?
I should 've put a rock at the closet door , too .
Death is the end . Right Father ?
When you 're dead , you 're dead ?
See ?
Vampires are not immortal .
You still want my blood ?
You want to see this dark world that badly ?
You live on other 's blood
but won 't give me a drop of yours !
Give me absolution and I 'll give it to you .
God the Father of mercies , has reconciled the world to himself
through the death and resurrection of his Son ...
and sent the Holy Spirit among us for the forgiveness of sins ;
through the ministry of the Church may God give you pardon and peace ...
and I absolve you from your sins in the name of the Father ...
and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit .
Amen .
Let us praise the Lord .
The Lord 's mercy endures forever .
The Lord has forgiven your sins .
Living as a vampire is like ...
Well , in one word ...
I feel like I 've been chosen .
I wasn 't neglected , after all !
I feel like I 've been given a special role in this life .
What role ?
I 've no idea .
Maybe to love a married woman .
If I live truthfully as a vampire , maybe I 'll find out some day .
Please .
In the name of the Father , the Son , and the Holy Spirit .
Amen .
I pray to Tae-ju .
Please wake up and listen to my prayer .
I said Kang-woo was drunk from a bottle of So-ju .
So say the same to the cops .
When this is all over we will be together .
We must not meet for a while .
Though my face may seem cold and rigid ...
my heart only beats for you .
When we meet again I believe we 'll finally be happy .
In the name of the Father , the Son In the name of the Father , the Son
Father ?
Doing it this way ...
feels like Ill live on inside you .
Stop all the ...
thinking , longing .
The police needs the body to close the case .
Kang-woo couldn 't swim , Mrs. Ra You gotta move on with your life .
Kang-woo can swim .
Father Hyun 's still not taking calls ?
It must 've been a big shock .
Still , he could 've come to the funeral .
Kang-woo !
I 'm Sang-hyun , Ma 'am .
I know I 'm all wet but ...
My poor baby .
What took you so long ?
Why didn 't you call ?
Bastard ! You son of a bitch !
- Mrs. Ra ! - Mrs. Ra !
Wake up Mrs. Ra !
Drink this , Mrs. Ra !
This is why we should all watch our blood pressures .
Watch our drinking .
And stay away from salty foods .
Let 's give Mrs. Ra our positive energy , Oasis-style .
Starting with Tae-ju .
Mom ...
How long 's it been ?
Why are you so wet ?
What ?
Is there a leak ?
Whys it so damp ?
Come here and stop imagining things .
It 's all psychological .
Stop making a fuss and will you come here ?
Was he here , too ?
He ? Who ?
I Seagulls flying in the distance ...
Don 't fall for it .
It 's all just an illusion .
It 's just psychological .
How 's that ?
You look pretty ...
Hello ?
A lie detector ?
Take this for now ...
What 's this for ... ?
She 's visiting her parents ...
It 's not easy for a woman to be alone ...
with your body getting all hot , yeah ?
You 're going ?
How can someone do it five times , straight ?
Mom never once threw me a birthday party .
How dare you !
But she always gave me plenty to eat .
Then thank her .
Thank you .
Can 't you go to that detective ?
Aren 't you thirsty these days ?
I 'll throw you a birthday party this year .
Really ?
The first birthday party in my life ?
But ... I don 't know when my birthday is .
But who made you boss ?
Telling me this and that
and hitting me around .
Kang-woo never laid a hand on me .
Did Kang-woo ...
beat you or not ?
Why does that matter ?
That 's why he died !
Don 't make excuses !
You would 've killed him anyway .
So you can have me for yourself .
Do you know how hard I tried not to kill people ?
You can 't even begin to imagine !
A blood thirsty beast is growling inside me !
But I tiptoed around afraid to hurt anyone .
I killed him cuz of you .
To save you .
To save me ?
Then why am I living a nightmare ?
I stay up trembling at the thought of
your cold hand touching me .
How did this happen ?
Mom !
I 'm done for .
He 's going to kill me .
Poor Kang-woo ...
My poor , dear mom ...
You treated that devil like a son and this is what you get ?
Did I do it alone ?
It was your idea .
No ! It was his idea !
He said he 'll kill the mother and son !
Honest !
I 'm sorry . Please forgive me .
We were a happy family of three till you infested us !
You 're a germ !
You said I was cute , you cunt !
Mommy , mommy ...
Look at me .
You can 't die like this .
Mom .
Tell me you forgive me .
Mom ...
Look at me .
If you forgive me blink once .
Just one blink ? Please ?
Just once ? Please ?
Let 's go !
That devil will suck all the blood out of you , too !
Let go !
Stay back you devil !
I want to go to Kang-woo .
Kill me , please .
You want to go ?
Go to your husband ?
Really ?
Happy birthday , Tae-ju .
The sun 's down already ?
Completely white just like daylight .
That 's a good girl .
From now on , we wear shoes inside the house like in the States .
Cuz I 'm in charge , now .
You have to sleep during the day , too .
And eat at night ...
Did you just move ?
Watch TV while I 'm out .
A scary movies gonna be on .
You shouldn 't look at this .
Do you love Tae-ju Park ?
Of course not .
I heard the priest came by all too often to the house ...
what is your relationship with him ?
I didn 't like the priest from the beginning .
Take a cab home .
They 'll suspect us if we leave together .
Should it matter which route I take ? I 'll get there in time ...
I just wondered whereabouts you are .
I 'm going up the hill on the highway ...
Why did you want to see so urgently ?
- It 's about the polygraph test earlier ... - Yeah .
I just remembered something else .
You did ?
It 's about Father Hyun ...
I 'm not ashamed at all !
I told you !
Ill get the blood !
Stealing from the hospital ?
- There 's more . - What ?
I 'm helping people who want to commit suicide .
I know many people like that from listening to confessions .
If I run out , I 'll find more through the Internet .
They face death more peacefully if I help them .
If they just give it to you , what fun is that ?
It tastes much better this way .
How many has to die for your taste ?
Maybe around 5007 ? How 's that , Father ?
I told you I 'm not a Father anymore !
Oh dear , the Father is mad .
Stop acting so humane ! You 're not even human .
Then what are we ?
We 're human-eating beasts that 's what !
Is it a sin for a fox to eat a chicken ?
Don 't make me regret saving you .
Kill me or save me you 'll regret either way .
We 're through !
I dump him and he drops me like this ?
You 're the only one I 've got , now .
Then let me eat what I want .
No !
No ? Even if I die ?
You said women are safe from EV .
Your blood is completely mixed with mine .
Then , I 'm no longer a woman ?
Hold on .
I 'll get a doctor .
Hello ?
How do you feel ...
Tae-ju ...
What day is it today ?
The eyes are so telling .
They can express everything between yes and no .
What good is just a yes or no ?
You need a subject and verb to communicate .
The subject is what 's being stared at .
If you stare at something for over 4 seconds ...
others will automatically turn to look , too .
Is that a published theory ?
Haven 't had the chance yet .
I 'm an expert at reading the eyes after 2 years of marriage
That 's why her Korean 's not improving .
Can you tell what mom 's saying ?
That 's what I 'm talking about !
Tae-ju just saw me peek over at Mrs. Ra .
She knew what I was going to say , before I said it .
By glancing at my eyes .
Mrs. Ra said I 'd win if I took this piece .
And that she wants some Vodka .
Vodka !
I win !
Closed , Self-draw , bonus 3 points ,
Big three dragons !
See that ?
Thank you , Mrs. Ra .
You want to play that bad ?
How about teaming her up with Evelyn ?
If you blink it means ' yes ' .
A long blink means ' no ' .
Okay ?
Blink if you understand .
Throw it away .
Mrs. Ra is back !
Evelyn ? Vodka .
' D ' .
' D ' , what ?
You can move your finger , mom ?
What 's wrong with your nail ?
' L ' It 's another letter !
What ?
' L , D " .
Or ' D , L ' ?
' D ' comes last , ' LD " .
Maybe she wants the ' LCD " on ?
There 's probably a ' C ' somewhere .
' C ...
Found it !
- ' K ' - ' K ' ?
L. D. K ?
Ladies Delaying , Killing the game .
' D ' comes last ! ' KLD "
Mrs. Ra , it 's ' DKL " ' , right ?
She says , no .
' KLD ' ? ' KILLED ' " ?
I 'm right ?
See ? It 's ' KILLED "
Whatever , let 's keep the game alive .
- Whose turn is it ? - Killed who ?
Mahjong brings back memories of Kang-woo ?
Mom ... it 's not your fault .
He didn 't die cuz of you .
Stop playing and go to bed .
Tae-ju 's so strong .
Stop torturing yourself
Look at me , Mrs. Ra .
It was an accident .
No one killed Kang-woo .
It 's not like Tae-ju and Sang-hyun killed ...
Selfish humans .
Bastards coming to play Mahjong with a grieving family
What ?
Why you little shit .
I 'm leaving , cuz shit smells not scares .
Honey ! No !
Oh , Young-du .
Young-du !
Stop it .
You easy-blood drinking coward .
It 's cuz he 's dead and the heart stopped pumping .
Cut off the ankles and ...
hang them over the bathtub and let gravity do the rest .
We can put the blood in tupperware and keep it in the fridge
I thought of using a motor pump but this works best .
Sucking a little and throwing the body away is
treating life too lightly , isn 't it ?
Evelyn ...
How could I have made all those Kimbaps without you ?
It 's over now .
Happy ?
Tae-ju .
Listen to me carefully .
Why do I have to run away ?
From my own house ?
Won 't they search the house when they find the 4 people missing ?
While they search around the house ,
if they open the wardrobe and the curtains in daylight ,
then we 'll die ?
What are you doing ?
You already had your fill .
They 'll barge into the house
without dusting off their shoes ...
What will happen to the house ?
Where are you going ?
The sun 's coming up !
Didn 't you have your fill from Evelyn ?
Won 't you ever answer me ?
I wanted to live with you forever and ever .
Together again in hell then .
When you 're dead , you 're dead .
It 's been fun , Father